(Howard:)with you
all the way to morning.
(Howard:)Unless the desert air
dries out her sinuses,
(Howard:)in which case I'll have
to schlep out there
(Howard:)with the big humidifier.
(Bernadette:)That's it?
(Bernadette:)That's your big solution
to all of our problems?
(Bernadette:)If your mom's nose holds up,
we get two nights together?
(Howard:)Isn't that great?
(Bernadette:)No, it's not great.
(Bernadette:)You need to make a choice.
(Bernadette:)Me or your mother.
(Leonard:)Uh...
(Bernadette:)Wrong answer.
(Howard:)No, wait.
(Howard:)You didn't let me finish.
(Bernadette:)I'm listening.
(Leonard:)Uh...
(Amy:)I came as quickly as I could.
(Howard:)Okay.
(Leonard:)Why?
(Amy:)To comfort you, of course.
(Amy:)Sheldon told me about Leonard
dating Rajesh's sister.
(Amy:)So I high-tailed it over here
(Amy:)to pick up the pieces
of your broken heart.
(Penny:)Amy, I'm fine.
(Amy:)You don't have to
be strong for me.